（1641年 法国）
詹姆斯·麦卡伦 你这只苏格兰猪
James McCullen, you Scottish pig,
你因向我们法兰西国王路易十三的敌人
you've been found guilty of treason for the sale of military arms
贩卖军火而被裁定为叛国罪
to the enemies of our Lord, King Louis XIII,
甚至同时你也在向吾王出售军火
even whilst you sold arms to our Lord himself.
你们的国王只是个连盟友都杀害的无耻渣滓
Your king is a vile bag of filth who murders his own allies.
我应当将他加倍控诉
I should have charged him double.
你企图和吾王的敌人合谋颠覆他的统治
You tried to overthrow the Crown in conspiracy with its enemies.
和你们的蠢蛋国王不同 他的敌人们明白
Unlike your simpleton king, his enemies know
麦卡伦的真正使命 并不是简单的兜售军火
that it is the true McCullen destiny not simply to supply arms,
而是引发战争！
but to run the wars!
你在刑罚执行之前还有别的话说吗？
Do you have anything else to say before the sentence is carried out?
对 我有
Yes, I do.
克兰·麦卡伦比你们当中任何人想象的
Clan McCullen is far greater and more powerful
都要伟大和强大
than any of you could ever imagine.
我的子嗣们在我死后将会长久地崛起
My sons will continue to rise long after I am gone,
他们的子孙也会
as will their sons
如神应允 就会生生不息
and, God willing, their sons.
我的死不会带来终结
It shall not end with my death!
我们并不打算杀你 麦卡伦
We are not going to kill you, McCullen.
我们要给你做个标志！
We're going to make an example of you!
这样就没有人 不论男女老幼 都不再看到你这叛徒的嘴脸
So that no man, woman nor child may ever see your treacherous face again,
你的余生都将戴着这个面具度日
you shall wear this mask for the term of your natural life.
不！不！不！
No! No! No! No!
《特种部队：眼镜蛇的崛起》
（在不远的将来）
（北大西洋公约组织武装指挥部）
在近四个世纪以来 我的祖先们…
For nearly four centuries, my ancestors have been
一直都是这世上最伟大的武器发明家
the greatest creators of weaponry in the world.
但或许在这个世纪 我将超越所有先人
But perhaps in this century, I'll outdo them all.
纳米虫 完美的微型战士
Nanomites, perfect little soldiers
最初为分割并杀死癌细胞而设计
originally developed to isolate and kill cancer cells.
但在MARS工业
But at MARS Industries,
以及在北约给予的一些赞助下
and with the help of a little NATO funding,
我们发现了使它们无所不能的方法
we discovered how to program them to do almost anything.
举个例子 啃蚀金属
For example, eat metal.
请看世界上第一枚纳米虫弹头实验
Watch this test of the world's first nanomite warhead.
每一枚这样的弹头 包含七百万个纳米虫
Each of these warheads contains 7 million nanomites
拥有着能够侵蚀掉任何东西的能力
and has the ability to eat anything from a single tank
不论坦克还是一座城市
to an entire city.
如同所见 它将迅速地开始啃蚀 它接触到的所有物体和材料
As you can see, it quickly converts to eating any and all material in its path.
一经释放 纳米虫将不会停歇 永远不会
Once unleashed, the nanomites will not stop, ever.
一旦目标被摧毁…
Once the target has been destroyed,
使用者可以通过唯一的 与每个弹头配对的开关
the launcher triggers a kill switch unique to each warhead
来短路掉纳米机器人 以防止不必要的破坏
that short-circuits the nanomites, preventing any unwanted destruction.
先生们 我很高兴地宣布 明天早上
Gentlemen, I'm pleased to announce that tomorrow morning,
你们纳米科技弹头的首批订单 将会从我在吉尔吉斯斯坦的工厂运出
your first order of nanotech warheads ships from my factory in Kyrgyzstan.
武器箱正在转移 预计2分钟后交给北约小队
Weapons case on the move. ETA two minutes to NATO team.
（吉尔吉斯斯坦 MARS武器综合车间）
好了 听着 北约老板要的是精英中的精英
All right, listen up. NATO wants the best of the best.
所以我们才在这儿 我们前后都有豹式装甲车护送
That's why we're here. We got Panthers front and back.
犀牛装甲车载着包裹走中间
RHINO's carrying the package in the middle.
全程相互保持最小距离 阿帕奇战机将在我们上方护送
Minimum distance at all times. Apaches are covering us from overhead.
详述完毕 立正 解散 伙计们
Detail, attention. Fall out, boys.
豪瑟上尉 麦卡伦先生要您在这签名
Captain Hauser, Mr. McCullen requires a signature.
这玩意儿不会炸吧 对吗？
Not gonna explode, is it?
它们还没有被激活 短路器都在里面
They're not weaponized yet, and the kill switches are inside.
尽管如此 我是你的话就会尽量避免颠簸
All the same, I'd avoid potholes if I were you.
- 嘿 比尔？- 嗯？
- Hey, Bill? - Yeah?
把它放在犀牛上 好吗？
Put that in the RHINO, would you?
好了 小妞们！上车！
All right, ladies! Mount up!
好了 阿帕奇 货已装车 保持警惕
Okay, Apaches, we're heavy, so keep your eyes open.
明白 这里到甘奇空军基地的上空畅通无阻
Roger that. Skies are clear all the way to Ganci.
- 嘿 公爵 我一直在想 - 我之前提醒过你
- Hey, Duke, I've been thinking. - You know, I warned you about that.
我在想我们该把这转移给谁
I've been thinking about where we should transfer to.
- 别说是空军 - 就是空军！
- Don't say the Air Force. - The Air Force!
我怎么说的？我以为这个讨论已经结束了
What did I say? I thought we were done with this conversation.
你的发言结束了 我还没
You were done with this conversation, not me.
你知道 我的飞行史…
You know, I've been flying
- …从13岁开始 - 13岁开始
- since I was 13 years old. - Thirteen years old.
我觉得开你爸的农药喷洒机 不能算进去
You know, I don't think your dad's crop-duster counts as hours logged.
我说的是喷气机 老兄 喷气机！
I'm talking jets, man. Jets.
而你知道我每次休假都有资格飞的
And you know I qualify every time we're on leave.
- 你想到天上去？- 对
- You want to get up in the air? - Yeah.
- 我给你买个蹦床吧 - 我都填过申请表了
- I'll buy you a trampoline. - I filled out the application.
真的？他们接受了那些蜡笔鬼画符？
Really? They accept those in crayon?
拜托 老兄 给我一个不飞的好理由
Come on, dude. Give me one good reason why not.
因为我想在战场里面 在战斗中 而不是飞在上空
'Cause I want to be on the ground, in the fight, not flying over it.
先锋1 这里是先锋2 启动夜视模式
Pioneer 1, this is Pioneer 2, going night vision.
- 明白 - 执行并后退
- Roger that. - Go ahead and back off.
腾出点安全距离
Give me some separation.
先锋1 这里是先锋2 已启动夜视模式
Pioneer 1, this is Pioneer 2. Going NVS.
明白
Roger.
嘿 公爵 我们不是定好
Hey, Duke, weren't we supposed to meet up
和侦查小队在40公里处会合的吗？
with the recon team at 40 klicks?
- 对 怎么了？- 呃 我们刚经过了第41公里
- Yeah. So? - Well, we just passed kilometer 41.
- 小心 小心！- 周围什么都没有 长官
- Eyes out, eyes out! - Sweep's still clear, sir.
收到 这里除了我们没别人
Roger that. There's nothing up here but us.
汤姆 发射曳光弹并开始自行搜索…
Tom, put a self-test on the flare and start to scan for…
我的…
Holy…
那该死的是什么？
What the hell is that?
先锋1 你中弹了！
Pioneer 1, you've been hit.
停车！
Stop!
- 大鸟坠毁！大鸟坠毁！- 后退！后退！
- Bird down! Bird down! - Back up! Back up! Back up!
各单位 我们遭到袭击！他们是抢弹头的！
All units, we are under attack! They're after the warheads!
先锋2 交火！
Pioneer 2, engage!
- 把那混蛋给我打下来！- 收到！给点颜色这家伙看看
- Put that asshole on the ground! - Roger that. Put some hurt on this guy!
机载机枪 正在开火 正在开火！
Tommy guns. Firing, firing, firing!
- 导弹待发 - 锁定发射
- Missiles armed. - Match and shoot.
锁定发射！导弹发射！
Match and shoot! Missiles off!
他们在空中把导弹打掉了！
They shot them right out of the air.
哦我的上帝
Oh, my God.
- 先锋2坠毁！我们失去制空权！- 我们被合围了！
- Pioneer 2 is down! We've lost our air! - They're boxing us in!
各单位 散开！我重复 各单位 散开！
All units, fan out! I repeat, all units, fan out!
地对空导弹瞄准这家伙！发射！发射！
I want SAMs on that thing! Light him up! Light him up!
它掉头回来了 50毫米炮瞄准它！
He's coming around. Get those.50s on him!
打过来啦！
Incoming!
抓稳！
Hold on!
没事吧？
You okay?
嗯 但我的脚卡住了 那玩意儿是什么？
Yeah, but my leg is pinned. What the hell was that?
- 快 我们要加入战斗 - 小心 我的脚！
- Come on, we gotta get in this fight. - Careful, my leg!
加油 伙计 我们上 起来 快！
Come on, buddy, let's go. Let's go, get up, come on!
公爵 我们要先拿到那些弹头！
Duke, you gotta go get those warheads!
闭嘴！我要先带你离开这里
Shut up! I gotta get you out of here first!
向空旷地带开火！右翼！右翼！
Fire at the opening! Right side, right side!
起来 起来 起来！
Get up, get up, get up, get up!
我该死的腿！
My damn leg!
- 你呆在这儿 明白？- 你要去哪儿？
- You wait here, okay? - Where are you going?
我要去拿那箱子
I gotta go get that case.
空军 没错
Air Force, right.
别动！
Don't move!
- 你好啊公爵 - 安娜？
- Hello, Duke. - Ana?
现在你必须承认 这是你自找的
Now, you have to admit, you had that coming.
安娜！
Ana!
（已记录目标）
（回卷中）
（目标锁定）
拜拜
Bye-bye.
安娜！安娜！
Ana! Ana!
别逼我对女人开枪
Don't make me shoot a woman.
炮火来袭！
Incoming!
后退 都给我后退！
Stand down. Stand the hell down!
- 放下武器 先生 - 我们不是敌人
- Put the weapon down, sir. - We're not the enemy.
用武器对准我是不能和我交朋友的 不是吗？
Pointing your weapons at me doesn't make you my friend, now, does it?
请把箱子交出来 先生
Please hand over the case, sir.
我不认识你 而且我也很肯定不认识那帮人
I don't know you, and I sure as hell don't know who they are,
除非我搞清楚 否则我不会放下任何东西
and until I find out, I'm not lowering anything
也不会交出任何东西
and I ain't handing anything over.
如果不是我们出手 你的下场就和你其他的手下一样
If it weren't for us, you'd be out there with the rest of your boys.
- 所以请交出那箱子 - 你是哪个队伍的？
- So hand over the case. - What's your unit?
那是机密
That's classified.
有人想和你谈谈
Someone would like to have a word with you.
报上你的姓名和军阶
State your name and rank.
- 你先说 - 我的部下刚刚救了你的命 小子
- You first. - My team just saved your life, son.
现在该到你说谢谢的时候了
This is the part where you get to say thank you.
这两个字不是我现在想说的
Those aren't the words that come to mind right now.
我没收到任何消息说这次行动会有支援
I wasn't told anything about any support for this mission,
所以为什么不让你的手下先退下呢？
so why don't you tell your team to stand down?
在我看来你们就像大大的活靶子
We could turn this into one big turkey shoot.
没错
Yep.
或别的
Or not.
放松 开伞索
Easy, Ripcord.
- 你怎么认识我的？- 杰出枪手
- How do you know me? - Expert marksman,
你们营排名第二 武器专家 持有喷气机驾照
second in your battalion. Weapons specialist, jet qualified.
- 我和你说过 - 现在别闹 开伞索
- I told you. - Not now, Rip.
我是克莱顿·阿博纳西将军 你可能听说过我 公爵
My name is General Clayton Abernathy. Perhaps you've heard of me, Duke.
霍克将军 阿富汗 北约前线指挥官
General Hawk. Afghanistan, NATO forward command.
对 那是我上一份工作 我现在穿上不同的军装了
Yeah, that was my last job. I'm in a whole new outfit now.
嘿 只是为了安全起见 我要关掉里面的追踪信号器
Hey, I just need to deactivate the tracking beacon for security.
把武器箱放下 小子 让我们来送这些弹头
Put down that weapons case, son, and let us deliver those warheads.
没门 我接受了这个任务
No way. I signed for them.
是我的使命 我的包裹 我接手了 我就送达
It's my mission, my package. I carry them, I deliver them.
嗯 那好吧 不过你现在看起来好像缺少交通工具
Well, that's just fine, but you seem to be a little short of transportation right now,
所以我的A小队会把你送来我这儿
so my Team Alpha will deliver you to me.
那你确切的位置在哪儿 长官？
And where exactly are you, sir?
你自己来看吧
Come see for yourself.
我以为你们特别行动组的人都是猛男
I thought all you Special Ops guys were tough.
我们是猛男 不过我们也很敏感体贴
We are tough. But we're also sensitive.
我来就好 谢谢
I got it. Thanks.
哇 这些东西真先进
Wow, this is some primo stuff here.
嘿 老兄 你这些头发可真逼真
Hey, bro, you got some real lifelike hair over there.
还会擒拿手
And a kung fu grip.
- 躺下 - 好吧
- Lie down. - Okay.
这么说来 这些都是什么制服？
What kind of outfit is this, anyway?
你们不是普通部队的 听你们口音就知道
It's not regular Army, based on all the accents.
你是英国腔 你的呢 北非法语？
You're British. What are you, French North African?
摩洛哥 你出生在哪儿？
Morocco. Where were you born?
公爵不是生出来的 他是政府发行的
Duke wasn't born. He was government-issued.
- 那你呢？- 他不说话
- What about you? - He doesn't speak.
- 为什么？- 他不说话
- Why? - He doesn't say.
他不说话 那不管怎样你们都是一个部队的
He doesn't say. So, somehow you're all in the same unit,
一个不能告诉我名字的部队 对吗？
but one you can't tell me the name of, right?
说了我们会被驱逐
We'd get tossed for telling.
你们不会放过那些袭击我们的人吧？
You're gonna go after those guys that hit my convoy, huh?
呃 不管你们是谁 你们属于哪个部队
Well, whoever you are and whatever this unit is,
我要加入
I want in.
将军
General.
- 还好吗 姑娘？- 干得好 特种兵们
- What's up, girl? - Good job, Joes.
非常出色
Outstanding.
欢迎来到地下基地 公爵 你们俩我久仰大名
Welcome to the Pit, Duke. I've read a lot about you two.
你不该相信你听说的东西 听着 实际上我…
Well, you can't believe everything you read. See, I actually…
我明白 几年前我曾试图招募你们
I understand we even tried to recruit you a few years back.
- 我从没收到加入任何行动组的邀请 - 真的？
- I never got asked to join any Op group. - Really?
你不记得4年前在泰国的事了？
You don't remember Thailand about four years ago?
就在你砸了那家酒吧之前？
Right before you broke up that bar?
大概4年前 我的伙计有点私事
About four years ago, my boy had issues.
我是说 他的私事出了点事
I mean, his issues had issues.
我一辈子都在军队里
I've been in the military my entire life
而我从没见过这样的作战行动组
and I have never seen a tac operation like this.
好吧 你相信了我 我想我也该相信你
All right, you trusted me, I guess I'll trust you.
严格地说 特种部队并不存在 如果存在
Technically, G.I. Joe does not exist, but if it did,
它就是由世上最顶尖的…
it'd be comprised of the top men and women
军事部队里的精英男女所组成的 王牌部队！
from the best military units in the world, the alpha dogs.
当所有人都失败时 我们不会
When all else fails, we don't.
最初有10个国家加入我们
Ten nations signed on in our first year,
一起行动 分享情报 迄今为止已有23个成员国
working together, sharing intel. Now we have 23.
- 那是什么？- 电子迷彩服
- What's that? - Camouflage suit.
他能把你身后的景物投影到身前
It photographs everything behind you and puts it in front of you.
- 麦卡伦先生已经准备好了 长官 - 用全息投影通话把他接进来
- Mr. McCullen is standing by, sir. - Patch him through via TelePresence.
- 那么谁打了我们？- 暂时未知
- So who hit us? - Currently unknown.
但有一点是肯定的
But one thing's for sure,
她能得到最高机密的情报和最新式的武器
she's got highly classified intel and state-of-the-art weaponry,
说明她背后有着庞大的资金支柱
which means there's a whole hell of a lot of money behind her.
他们拥有我们之前从未遇到过的实力
Their capabilities are beyond anything we've ever encountered.
对 那就是我们被当场打得屁滚尿流的 唯一理由
Yeah, that's the one and only reason why we got our asses kicked out there.
我们必须尽可能找到有关她的一切情报
We need to find out everything we can about her.
知彼知己是作战的一部分
Knowing is half the battle.
先生们 这是麦卡伦先生
Gentlemen, Mr. McCullen,
MARS工业集团的首席执行官 也是这些弹头的制造者
CEO of MARS Industries and the builder of these warheads.
将军 看起来我当初应该选择你 来执行这次任务
General, clearly you were the security option I should have chosen.
你说的什么话？我的队员为了这次任务都拼了命
What did you just say? My team did everything we could out there,
- 很多好士兵都送了命 - 对 但你没有
- and a lot of good men went down. - Yeah, but not you.
这次行动是绝密的 所以很明显有人出卖了我们
That mission was classified, so clearly someone sold us out.
我用了10年时间和130亿欧元 来造这4枚弹头
I spent 10 years and 13 billion euros creating these four warheads.
而你的工作 上尉 就是保护它们
Your job, Captain, was to protect them,
如果不是多亏了霍克将军 你早就失败了
and if it wasn't for General Hawk, you'd have failed.
这样的评价并不公平 他完全执行了收到的命令
That's not a fair assessment. He followed his orders to the letter.
嗯 但那并不够
Well, that wasn't enough.
好了 为了不让袭击你们的混蛋找到你们
Now, so the bastards who attacked you can't find you,
你须要把藏在箱子里的追踪信号器关掉
you need to disable the tracking beacon hidden in the case.
- 我们已经关了 - 好样的
- We already have. - Good man.
不过还是让我检查一下有没有什么损坏吧
But allow me to check them to see if any have been damaged.
请把它打开
Open it, please.
我的探测器显示它们完好无损 先生
My scan says they're intact, sir.
- 密码是什么？- 「529440」
- What's the code? - 5-2-9-4-4-0.
[法语] 谢谢
请时刻让我知道你们的进展 将军
Please keep me informed of your progress, General.
断路器？
Breaker?
我的声音分析器显示他上下左右摇摆不定
My voice analyzer on that guy was going up, down and sideways.
看起来麦卡伦先生正在忙一些 不想让我们知道的事
Looks like McCullen's working an angle he don't want us to catch.
快没时间了 我们现在就需要那些弹头！
We're on a deadline. We need those warheads now!
你也知道的 用了10年来策划这件事…
You knew that! Ten years setting this up,
从北约那里榨取投资 现在这一步应该是最简单的啊
wringing money out of NATO, this was supposed to be the easy part.
如果你当初让我在你宝贝工厂 发动进攻的话
If you had let me stage the assault at your precious factory,
我就能完全掌控局势
I could have contained the situation.
然后立刻就让客户失去对我们的信任
And lost the trust of our clients in the process.
必须要让北约负这个责任！
It had to be NATO's fault!
怎么回事？
What happened?
- 你看到他的时候犹豫了？- 没有
- Did you hesitate when you saw him? - No.
这和他一点关系没有
This had nothing to do with him.
原谅我的嫉妒
Forgive my jealousy.
你追踪到那个箱子没？
Have you tracked the case?
他们当然关闭了导向信号器
They, of course, deactivated the homing beacon.
我给了他们一个神不知鬼不觉的激活密码
I gave them a code to quietly reactivate it.
地点在埃及 地下基地 只是有传言说过
It's in Egypt. The Pit, only mentioned in whispers.
我会把弹头取回来的
I will get those warheads back.
希望如此
I hope so.
如果我在你旁边 或许我会允许你碰我的
If I were really there, I might actually let you touch me.
- 我可以派飞机接你 - 先办公事吧
- I'll send a jet. - Business first.
况且 我是有夫之妇 记得吗？
Besides, I'm married, remember?
如果你当初派我去 可能早就完工了
If you had sent me in the first place, it would already be done.
我现在就派你去 白幽灵 别再失败了
I'm sending you now, Storm Shadow. No more mistakes.
计划不能再受到影响了
The schedule mustn't be compromised any further.
帮我把她看好
Keep your eye on her for me.
美国政治州长参议院国会议员
American politics, governors, senators, congressmen.
难怪什么事也办不了
No wonder nothing ever gets done.
那就是我们要解决的 扎坦先生
That's what we're going to fix, Mr. Zartan.
眼镜王蛇 高贵的生物
The king cobra, magnificent creature.
大自然的死神 以及致命企图的象征
Nature's Grim Reaper and symbol of lethal purpose.
它不出击则无法明视
Unseen until it strikes.
只要一口 它的毒液就能把一只成年大象毒死
Its venom can kill a full-grown elephant with a single bite.
- 非常好 - 迄今为止我们制造了20个尼奥蛇魔了
- Very nice. - So far we've created 20 Neo-Vipers.
- 其中19个站在你面前 - 有效吗？
- Nineteen stand before you. - Is it working?
我们给每个实验对象都注射了1000毫升的 纳米虫溶液
We injected 1, 000 cc of the nanomite solution into each subject.
他们最终停止尖叫后
When they finally stopped screaming,
扫描显示它们大脑皮层的…
brain scans showed a complete inactivity
自我保护区域完全停止了活动
of the self-preservation region of the cortex.
讲英语吗 博士？
English, Doctor?
他们感觉不到恐惧
They feel no fear.
大脑皮层的神经簇群完全处于静止状态
Cortical nerve clusters show complete inactivity.
他们感觉不到疼痛 道德观念已经被抛离
They feel no pain. Concepts of morality are disengaged.
他们感觉不到后悔 感觉不到怜悯
They feel no regrets, no remorse.
纳米虫如同战斗机器般集结起来
The nanomites join together as a fighting mechanism,
首先阻断 然后排出眼镜蛇的毒液
first blocking, then expelling the cobra's venom.
他们完全服从命令吗？
And they're completely obedient?
当然
Of course.
现实世界的应用将是无止尽的
The real-world applications are endless.
那么 你来告诉我 这好用吗？
So, you tell me, is it working?
派一个小队去会合白幽灵与男爵夫人
Send a team to rendezvous with Storm Shadow and the Baroness.
如果成功了 特种兵们都不知道是谁袭击了他们
Consider it done. The Joes will never know what hit them.
第20个尼奥蛇魔已经在华盛顿特区安插好了
The 20th Neo-Viper is already set up in Washington, DC
在等待你的命令
and awaiting your signal.
你干的不错 你的研究终于派上用场了
You've done well. You've thrown the caber clear out of the yard.
总统地堡的工程也已经竣工了
Construction of the presidential bunker has also been completed.
现在 如果我们卖一枚弹头到黑市
Now, if we sold one warhead on the black market,
就能继续我的研究了
I could continue my research.
我感激你对科技的渴求 博士
I appreciate your thirst for knowledge, Doctor,
但这个世界已经够乱的了 不卖
but this world is messy enough. No.
它需要的是一个唯一的统领
What it needs is unification, leadership.
要有一个完全掌控的人 把它从混沌中解救出来
It has to be taken out of chaos by someone with complete control.
北京莫斯科华盛顿…
Beijing, Moscow, Washington…
当这些导弹被引爆
When these missiles detonate,
全世界都会向这世上最强大的人求救
the world will turn to the most powerful man on the planet.
当我成功之后 钞票会滚滚而来的
When I'm finished, the money will take care of itself.
你就可以作任何你想作的研究
You'll be able to do all the research you want.
我们从一个作战摄像头上捕捉到了这个影像
We grabbed this image from one of our tactical cameras.
现在我们对她的脸作一个全匹配扫描
Now we're running her face through an infinity scan.
嘿 这不是…
Hey, isn't that…
我们已经得到全世界 各个地方各个服务器上的照片
We have access to any photograph on any server, anywhere in the world.
对 每个人总会在某个地方某个时间 留下相片
Yep. Everyone gets photographed in some way at some time.
足球比赛自动提款机机场…
Football game, ATM machine, airport…
我们会找到她的 然后就知道是谁派她来的
We'll find her, and then we'll find out who sent her.
- 北约来电 长官 - 你还好吧？
- From NATO, sir. - Are you okay?
她到底怎么了？
What happened to her?
好了 看起来我已经被任命为 这些弹头的看管者了
Well, it appears that I've been made official custodian of the warheads.
你的任务应该就此结束了 公爵
Looks like your mission is complete here, Duke.
当你们转移它们时 她会找上门来的 你知道的吧？
When you move them, she's gonna come after you. You know that, right?
凭着她的情报和手下 她会找到你们的
And with her intel and toys, she'll find you.
你的意思是？
What's your point?
你要先发制人的话就让我们加入
You're going after her first and we want in.
将军 当场被灭的是我们小队 我们要报仇
General, it was our team that got wasted out there. We deserve payback.
特种部队不接受入队申请 只有被邀请
You don't ask to be part of G.I. Joe. You get asked.
4年前你考察过我 现在我准备好了 让我们开始吧
You scouted me four years ago. Now I'm ready. Let's have at it.
好吧 我也损失了人手 上尉
Well, I've lost men, too, Captain.
- 如果你想报仇… - 我认识她
- Lf you want revenge… - I know her.
你说什么？
Excuse me?
你说过知彼知己是作战的一部分 不是吗？
You said knowing's half the battle, right?
那好 我知道她是谁
Well, I know who she is.
她以前金发的 名字是安娜·刘易斯
She was a blonde. Her name is Ana Lewis.
我可以告诉你她的一切事情
I could tell you everything you need to know about her,
直到4年前
up until the last four years.
那之后很显然 很多事情变化了
After that, obviously, a lot of things have changed.
我妻子终于到家了
Finally, my wife is home.
好啊丹尼尔 你和国防部长的会议怎样了？
Hello, Daniel. How was your meeting with the Minister of Defense?
他十分激动 加速器表现得完美无瑕
He was thrilled. The accelerator performed flawlessly.
我真希望你当时也在场
I wish you would have been there.
你和你的实验室小家伙们真是聪明
You and your little lab rats are so clever.
- 蒙特卡洛好玩吗？- 我没有得到我追寻的东西
- How was Monte Carlo? - I didn't get what I was after.
- 我应当为此感到欣慰 - 大多数丈夫都是
- I suppose I should be grateful. - Most husbands would be.
大多数丈夫没有这么神秘的妻子
Most husbands don't have such mysterious wives.
他们清楚知道她们在哪儿 她们在干什么
They know exactly where they are and what they do.
他们以为知道
They think they know.
安娜 我不想斗嘴 我想你
Ana, I don't wanna fight. I missed you.
好吧 我从来不厌倦斗嘴
Well, I never tire of a good fight.
但不是和你 亲爱的 让我梳洗一下再到楼下找你
But not with you, darling. Let me freshen up and I'll meet you downstairs.
我是爱你的 我美丽的男爵夫人
I do love you, my beautiful Baroness.
麦卡伦给我命令 如果男爵再这么碰你我就会杀了他
McCullen gave me orders to kill the Baron if he so much as touched you.
他是我丈夫 他当然会碰我
Well, he's my husband. Of course he touches me.
再说 他实验室的工作 在我们有所触碰之后会进行得更好
And besides, his work at the lab goes much better after we've touched.
而那是件要紧的事
And that's the important thing.
那你在干什么？监视我吗？
So what are you doing? Spying on me?
如果我要监视你 你永远不会察觉到
If I was spying on you, you would never know.
我有进步了
Getting closer.
你曾是我最好的学生
You were my best student.
我会和你一起去取回弹头
I'll be coming with you to retrieve the warheads.
我们天亮出发
We go at dawn.
（4年前）
来 安娜
Come on, Ana.
好了 我一直想在部队集结前做这件事
Okay, so, I've been wanting to do this before we deploy.
公爵 太漂亮了 真是太漂亮了
Duke, it's beautiful. It's too beautiful.
既然我一生只须要买一个戒指 为什么不呢？
I'm only going to buy one of these, so why not?
你觉得怎样？
So what do you say?
说愿意啊傻瓜 这可是活生生的美国英雄啊
Say yes, you idiot. He's a real American hero.
多谢毁了这气氛 雷克斯
Thanks for ruining the mood, Rex.
我道歉 我是来接你回岗
I apologize. I just came to offer you a ride back to post.
什么？到时间了？
What? It's time already?
- 是啊我们要在5点整动身 - 这是…
- Yeah, we got to go at 0500. - Is it…
是啊没错 对吗？这就是你把雷克斯从实验室带出来的原因
Yeah, it is, right? That's why you're pulling Rex out of the lab.
- 安娜 听我说 很抱歉 但我不能… - 对 对 机密 最高机密
- Ana, look, I'm sorry, but I can't… - Yeah, yeah, classified, top secret,
如果和我说了就要杀我灭口 废话连篇
you'd have to kill me if you told me, blah-blah-blah.
说到机密信息
And speaking of classified information, you still haven't answered me.
你还没有给我答复
我愿意 我当然愿意
Yes. Yes. Of course it's yes.
但有一个条件
On one condition.
你必须向我保证 你不会让我的天才
You have to promise me that you will not let my genius,
书呆子弟弟受一点伤
egghead brother get hurt.
他是我仅有的家人了
He's the only family I've got left.
向我保证 公爵
Promise me, Duke.
我保证
I promise.
- 嘿 我最喜欢三个家伙 - 威姆斯先生 还好吗？
- Hey! My three favorite people. - Mr. Weems. Good, man?
- 不错 - 看
- Yeah. - Look.
哇 石头不错 真是份厚爱啊
Wow. Nice rock. That's a lot of love.
- 你在求婚？- 其实我求完婚了
- Are you proposing? - I'm actually done proposing.
- 我也说过愿意了 - 我的天 恭喜你们！
- I already said yes. - Oh, my God! Congratulations!
漂亮极了！你们俩就像婚礼蛋糕上那对白色小人
Beautiful! You guys are like the little white couple on the wedding cake.
太可爱了 给我些爱吧
How cute. Give me some love.
恭喜你们 等等 这不是正式的
Congratulations. Wait. It's not official.
- 怎么了？- 不是正式的
- What? - It's not official.
- 除非你回答了我的问题 - 好吧
- Not until you answer my question. - Okay.
你爱不爱我的兄弟？
Do you love my boy?
一直爱 永远爱
Always and forever.
你们可能用了威胁的手段来加入这个队伍
You may have blackmailed your way onto this team.
并不意味我会喜欢这样
Doesn't mean I've got to like it.
但的确意味着 我必须让你们准备好接受任务
But it does mean I've gotta get you mission ready,
特种兵的方式
Joe style.
在你们面前的 是德耳塔-6型加速套装
Standing in front of you are Delta-6 Accelerator suits.
- 它给什么加速？- 你
- What does it accelerate? - You.
它会让你跑得更快 跳得更高 让你比任何敌人都更有力
It'll make you run faster, jump higher and hit harder than any of your enemies.
开始着装
Let's suit up.
这是从头到脚的水力学 和高度气密下的气体力学装备
Head-to-toe hydraulics and highly pressurized pneumatics.
这是个加强的智能控制显示头盔
An advanced cybernetics heads-up display helmet,
它与套装相连接
which feeds into the suit.
你有所想 它有所动
You think it, it does it.
双制气推式钩枪…
Twin gas-propelled grappling spears
和三倍爆炸力热导式射后不理式导弹
and triple-explosive, heat-seeking, fire-and-forget rockets.
还有我的个人最爱
And my personal favorite,
一把10毫米无弹壳格林机关枪
a 10-millimeter caseless Gatling submachine gun,
每分钟能够发射50发子弹 全自备式火力
capable of firing 50 rounds per second. Fully self-contained firepower.
十分适合像你们这样的菜鸟
Perfect for a couple of cowboys like you.
你刚说的我都错过了 嘿 我帅吗？
I just missed everything you said. Hey, how do I look?
- 挺酷的吧？- 有问题吗？
- Pretty cool, huh? - Any questions?
好啊巨石中士
Yo, Sergeant Stone.
- 他们是特种兵吗？- 才不是 他们是特种饼…
- Are they Joes? - Hell, no. They're jokes.
小子
Boys.
你会用上这个的
You're gonna need these.
只是想对你说 当我确定目标的时候
Just so you know, when I get a target in my sights,
我就会拿下它
I take it down.
该死！
Oh, shit!
- 再来 - 再来？
- Again. - Again?
只是想对你说 有些目标要相对的难以击中
Just so you know, some targets are harder to hit than others.
- 再来 - 你最好戴上那头盔
- Again. - You're gonna need that helmet.
退下吧 面具人
Stand down, Snake Eyes.
好吧 走吧 散场了 以后还有得看
All right. Walk away. It's over. This ain't pay-per-view.
我真是太棒了
I'm nasty with it!
有一个脱了靶
You missed one.
拜托 我肯定创下了记录
Come on. That gotta be some kind of a record or something.
- 记录是20个全中 - 谁创造的？让我猜猜
- The record is all 20 killed. - Who did that? Let me guess.
- 面具人？- 不 是我
- Snake Eyes? - No. Me.
如果你要向目标开火 就得彻底 否则 就要肉搏了
If you're gonna shoot at something, kill it. Otherwise, take up knitting.
（第99百分位）
初学者的运气 保持专注
Beginner's luck. Stay focused.
- 再来 - 再来？
- Again. - Again?
我从没见到面具人被打中过
I have never seen Snake Eyes take a hit.
他们是特种兵了
They're Joes.
或许
Maybe.
来吧
Let's go.
嘿 老兄 断路器告诉我红发女郎12岁就大学毕业了
Hey, man, Breaker told me that Scarlett graduated college at 12 years old.
她就像个难以捉摸的致命小天才
She's like some freaky little deadly genius.
- 开伞索 知道了 你喜欢她 - 抱歉 怪我
- Rip. I get it, Rip. You like her. - Sorry, my bad.
- 管它的 - 开伞索
- To hell with it. - Rip. Rip.
（构造原理）
「六百骑兵全部进入了死亡之谷」
Into the valley of death rode the 600.
嘿 你在干嘛呢？海边阅读吗？
Hey, what are you doing? A little beach reading?
好吧
Okay.
听我说 我想我们之间一开始就有些误会
Look, I think you and me got off on the wrong foot.
看 我被你吸引住了 而你 也被我吸引住了
See, I'm attracted to you. And you, you're attracted to me.
那个 那个大禅师
And him, the damn Zen master,
他让我直起疙瘩 我想说的意思是…
he creeps me out. What I'm trying to say is…
- 我们彼此被对方吸引 - 谢谢！
- We're attracted to each other. - Thank you!
这是你的意思 不是我的意思
That's what you're saying. It's not what I'm saying.
不是？
It's not?
那 你要说什么？
So, what are you saying?
被吸引是一种情感 情感无法用科学解释
Attraction is an emotion. Emotions are not based in science.
如果你不能量化那样事物 或证明它的存在 那么…
And if you can't quantify or prove that something exists, well,
在我看来 它就是不存在
in my mind, it doesn't.
好吧 我回头再和你讨论这个
Okay. I'll get back to you on that one.
立正！将军到！
Attention! General on deck!
稍息 公爵…
At ease. Duke,
你的成绩在我们考核过的所有人当中 名列前茅
you scored in the top half percent of all people we've ever tested.
开伞索 如果用你和公爵的分数 合起来对半分 你也合格了
Rip, if we average your scores with Duke's, you pass, too.
- 欢迎加入我们 - 谢谢 长官
- Welcome aboard. - Thank you, sir.
- 当然只是临时的 - 谢谢 长官
- Provisionally, of course. - Thank you, sir.
（无威胁）
长官 探测器检测到西南方有地震性活动
Sir, sensors detecting seismic activity to the southwest.
大概只是小地震 派一个小队去看看吧
Probably just a tremor, but have a team check it.
我们的小武器盒子在那儿
There's our little weapons case.
好了 你们三个 看好钻车
All right. You three, guard the machines.
- 打搅您很抱歉 长官 - 没关系 下士
- Sorry to disturb you, sir. - That's all right, Corporal.
这里需要您签名 这儿和这儿 还有这儿和这儿…
I need you to sign here, here and here. And also here, here…
再见了 宝贝
Goodbye, sweetheart.
对啊你从不杀女人
That's right. You don't kill women.
对于你 扎坦 我会网开一面
For you, Zartan, I'd make an exception.
是弹头 开伞索！快！
Warheads, Rip! Come on!
上！上！
Go, go!
我们拿到弹头了 预备好「鼹鼠号」准备撤退
We've got the warheads. Prep the Mole Pods for evac.
- 我们就到 - 已开始准备
- We're on our way. - We're already on it.
- 现在怎么离开这儿？- 跟我来
- Now how do we get out of here? - Follow me.
你想的美
Like that's gonna happen.
找到控制室 打开外部舱门
Find the control room. Open the exterior hatch.
- 并控制该区域 - 明白
- And secure this area. - We're on it.
安全
Clear.
上！上！
Go, go!
- 你会开这东西吗？- 别动！安娜 把箱子放下
- Can you fly one of these things? - Don't move! Ana, put the case down.
好 放下了
Fine. Done.
站住安娜 站那儿别动
Stop. Ana, stop right there.
- 你不会向我开枪的 不是吗？- 必要的话我会
- You can't shoot me, can you? - I will if I have to.
你心里 还是那个让我坠入爱河的男人
Deep down, you're still the same man I fell in love with.
- 别逼我 - 世事难料 不是吗 公爵？
- Don't force this. - What could have been. Right, Duke?
把箱子给我！该死的！
Just give me the case, God damn it.
- 动一动我就把她打飞 - 来吧 你已经杀过我一次了
- Move and I'm gonna blow her away. - Do it. You already killed me once.
公爵 小心！
Duke, watch out!
安娜 放下箱子！
Ana, drop the case!
好啊兄弟
Hello, brother.
该死！
Damn!
尝尝这个！
Eat this!
嘿 天才！
Hey, genius!
回见 公爵
See you, Duke.
- 有多少弹头？- 4个 总统先生
- How many warheads? - Four, Mr. President.
- 收到什么恐吓？要求？- 迄今为止没有 长官
- Any threats? Demands? - None so far, sir.
我们认为这说明恐怖分子还未统一意见
We take this to mean the terrorists are unfocused.
- 没有明确的目标 - 不
- No clear goals. - No.
这说明他们打算使用它们
It means they intend to use them.
霍克将军情况稳定了
General Hawk is stable now,
不过他可能要1天或更久才能醒来
but he won't be conscious for another day or so.
他是个硬汉
He's one tough bastard.
嘿
Hey.
- 你还好吧？- 我没事
- You all right? - I'm fine.
- 我不想让人看到我这个样子 - 怎么了？
- I didn't want anyone to see me like this. - Why?
说不清 损失好些兄弟 霍克将军受伤
I don't know. All the men we lost, General Hawk wounded,
我的脖子看起来就不重要了
my neck just doesn't seem important.
你刚才差点送了命 你有理由受到关怀
You almost lost your life out there. You have a reason to be concerned.
这是我从小到大第一次输
First fight I lost since I was a kid.
我爸爸教会了我去赢
My father taught me to win.
听我说 我不认为有人能教会别人 每一次每一件事都能胜出
Look, I don't see how you could teach anybody to win everything every time.
我是说 看看你
I mean, look at you.
你还活着 不是吗？
You're still here, right?
你被击倒了 就再站起来
You get knocked down, you get back up.
或许那才是他想你学会的东西
Maybe that's what he wanted you to learn.
但依然 那还是一种情感的反应
But then again, that would be an emotional response,
它无法被解释或量化
one that can't be explained or quantified.
嘿 看起来我们今天都见到鬼魂了
Hey. Looks like we're all seeing ghosts today, huh?
（东京 20年前）
[日语] 小贼！
白幽灵！
Storm Shadow!
[日语] 他偷东西吃
说英语 白幽灵 你的礼节呢？
English, Storm Shadow. Where are your manners?
他饿了
He is hungry.
我们要请他加入 指引他的方向
We need to invite him in and show him the path.
- 他是条野狗 是弱者 - 他打起来可不弱
- He is a cur, a weakling! - He does not fight like one.
好了 你叫什么名字？
Now, what shall we call you?
这是我一位祖先留下来的
This belonged to an ancestor of mine.
他因为向交战双方出售军火被捕
He was caught selling arms to both sides.
法国人迫使他戴着这个度过余生
The French forced him to wear it for the rest of his life.
他们叫他迪斯特罗 诸国毁灭者
They called him Destro, destroyer of nations.
那你为什么留着它？
So why do you keep it?
这样我才能记住军火买卖中的重要守则
So that I never forget the most important rule in dealing arms.
让我猜猜 永远不卖给交战的双方？
Let me guess. Never sell to both sides?
永远不要在卖的时候被抓到
Never get caught selling to both sides.
把弹头带到巴黎 激活它们
Take the warheads to Paris. Have them weaponized.
- 接着我要你测试一枚 - 测试一枚？
- Then I want you to test one. - Test one?
我要通过美国有线新闻网 让全世界看看它们表现有多好
We'll let CNN show the world how well they perform.
恐惧是一种强大的驱动力
Fear is a great motivator.
我有一个理想的目标 让法国人永世难忘的目标
I have a target in mind, one the French will never forget,
就像我永远忘不了 他们怎么对待克兰·麦卡伦一样
as I've never forgotten what they did to Clan McCullen.
- 准备好了吗 扎坦先生？- 生下来就准备好了 博士
- Are you ready, Mr. Zartan? - Born ready, Doctor.
这将会是我一生的伟大成就
This is going to be the achievement of a lifetime.
是的 作为一个伪装大师 你将无人能敌 我的朋友
Yes, as a master of disguise, you have no equal, my friend.
花了18个月来学习我的目标 学习他的小癖好
Eighteen months of studying my target, learning mannerisms,
越是细节越是险恶
but the devil is in the details.
先生们 我们开始吧
Gentlemen, let's get it going.
还有一件事
One more thing.
我的大脑由我控制 非常感谢合作
I'll control my own brain, thank you very much.
动手吧
Let's do this.
- 哇 有点让人不舒服 - 是吗？
- Wow. That was a bit nasty. - Think so?
我们作几个测试看看
Let's run some tests.
眼睛颜色 皮肤颜色 毛发分布
Eye color. Skin tone. Hair follicles.
开始面部重组测试
And initiating facial reconstruction tests.
我们要找到谁是他们背后的主子
We gotta find out who's holding their leash.
有着这样的装备资本和情报 这些家伙都是顶尖的专家
With their weaponry, financing and intel, these guys are high-line pros.
可选的答案就不多了
That limits the possibilities.
- 嘿 那个武器箱 - 什么？
- Hey, the weapons case. - What?
记得吗？麦卡伦让我们打开武器箱
Remember, McCullen had us open the weapons case?
- 那又如何？- 我打赌他当时给了我们一个…
- What about it? - I bet you he gave us a code
重新启动追踪信号器的密码
that reactivated the tracking beacon.
你说得对 麦卡伦 这狗娘养的
You're right. McCullen, that son of a bitch.
就是说 麦卡伦利用北约 资助他的武器研发
So, McCullen uses NATO to fund his R&D
然后又把那些弹头偷回去
and then he steals the warheads back.
- 谁说过你脑子不好使呢？- 嘿 我找到她了
- And who says you're not a thinker? - Hey, I found her.
对 没错是她
Yeah, that's her all right.
她名字是安娜·迪·科布雷 或者男爵夫人 如果你觉得这样正式点
Her name is Ana de Cobray. Baroness, if you're feeling formal.
男爵夫人？哇 她真找到了好东家 说的是钱 当然
Baroness? Wow, she really traded up, huh? Financially, of course.
- 这是谁？- 丹尼尔·迪·科布雷
- Who's he? - Daniel de Cobray.
法国科学家大亨 在巴黎有一间实验室
Big shot French scientist. Runs a lab in Paris.
- 实验室？什么实验室？- 粒子加速器
- Lab? What kind of lab? - Particle accelerator.
我的天 他们打算利用他来激活弹头
Oh, my God. They're going to use him to weaponize the warheads.
对 这就是她要去的地方
Well, that's where she's going.
我想吃羊角包
I like croissants.
- 上 上 上 上！- 快！我们上！我们上！
- Go, go, go, go! - Come on! Let's go! Let's go!
到那辆车那儿！
Pull up on the truck!
（东非 4年前）
上 上 上！
Go, go, go!
- 两点钟方向！- 上 上 上！
- Two o'clock! - Go, go, go, go, go!
上！快走！
Go, let's move!
- 到巷子里！- 蹲下！蹲下！
- In the alley! - Get down, get down!
看到敌人了吗？
You see them?
- 左翼还有两个！- 蹲下！
- Two more on the left! - Get down!
要泡泡糖？对我来说很有用
Dubble Bubble? It always helps me.
没错 嘿 你还好吧？
Yeah. Hey, you good?
- 是吧？- 还好
- Yeah? - Yeah.
好了 科研官 该你上了 明白？
All right, Mr. Science Officer, you're up, okay?
4分钟内找不到 就马上出来
You don't find it in four minutes, you get out of there.
5分钟后这座房子就会消失 我已经呼叫空袭了
That house will not be there in five. I already called for the air strike.
快！我们上！
Come on! Here we go!
你安全了！上 上 上！
I got you! Go, go, go, go!
我靠！
Oh, crap!
屋顶上！
Rooftop!
嘿 公爵 咱们比赛怎样？
Hey, Duke, I gotta level with you.
- 我最讨厌和你比赛 - 将会是漫长的5分钟
- I hate it when you level with me. - It's going to be a long five minutes.
不 不！来得太早了 太早了！
No, no, no! It's too early. It's too early!
- 公爵！- 雷克斯！雷克斯！
- Duke! - Rex! Rex!
雷克斯
Rex.
公爵！快来 要撤退了
Duke! Come on. We gotta go.
- 我要救雷克斯 - 要撤退了 老兄！
- I gotta get Rex. - We gotta go, man!
黑鹰直升机在等着！我们必须走！你无能为力的！
Black Hawk's waiting! We gotta go! Nothing you can do!
- 你无能为力 老兄！快！- 我要救雷克斯
- Nothing you can do, man! Come on! - I gotta get Rex.
预备 瞄准 开火
Ready. Aim. Fire.
向前 走！
Forward, march.
（巴黎 法国 早上8：25）
（迪·科布雷科学实验室）
你去登记还是我来？
Are you going to sign in or shall I?
安娜？
Ana?
这是谁？
Who is this?
嘿！你在干什么？
Hey! What are you doing?
- 这是怎么回事？- 我要你为我做些事
- What's going on here? - I need you to do something for me
而且是件急事
and I don't have much time.
这些是什么？
What are these things?
他们是武器弹头 亲爱的
They're warheads, dear.
而我须要你把它们激活 不然我会把这里的人杀光
And I need you to weaponize them for me, or we'll kill everyone in here.
嘿！这是个民用实验室！
Hey! This is a civilian laboratory!
我们没有激活武器所需的对应流程协议
We don't have the correct programming protocols for weaponizing!
协议就在箱子里 我说了 这是件急事
The protocols are in the case. I told you, I don't have much time.
嘿 是泡泡糖吗？
Hey, is that Dubble Bubble?
但这是最后一块了
But it's my last piece.
- 来吧 给我 - 好吧 拿着
- Come on, give it to me. - All right, there you go.
好啊照计划干 红发女郎 面具人 打头阵
All right. Stick to the plan. Scarlett, Snake Eyes, take the front.
开伞索 公爵 顾后 断路器就是我们耳目
Rip, Duke, take the back. Breaker will be our eyes and ears.
我会在这里下指令
I'll give the orders from here.
- 当我下命令时 照做 明白？- 明白 婆婆
- You do what I say, when I say. Got it? - Yes, Daddy.
好了
Here.
- 它们都激活了 - 谢谢 丹尼尔
- They're all alive. - Merci, Daniel.
我说过他再碰你我会杀了他
I told you I'd kill him if he touched you again.
第一次我就听你这么说了
I heard you the first time.
好了 我们就要到了
Okay, we're almost there. Scarlett, you better put your suit on.
红发女 你最好把装备穿上
就是她
That's her.
拿下那辆悍马 面具人！
Take that Hummer, Snake!
小心点 它们每件都值上百万美元
Careful. They're worth millions of dollars each.
百万美元 明白
Millions of dollars. Got it.
- 老天 - 我的错 我的错 下不为例！
- Jesus. - My bad. My bad. Won't happen again!
非常感谢 伙计
Thanks a lot, buddy!
快 红发女郎 宝贝 上还是不上？我们要马上进入战斗！
Come on, Scarlett, babe. You in or out? We gotta get in this fight!
追踪信号良好 抓牢那车别放 面具人
Tracking signal is good. Don't let go of that truck, Snake Eyes.
把那混蛋甩下车顶吧
Let's get that bastard off the roof.
小心！
Look out!
嘿 重载 情况有点不妙
Hey, Heavy, it's getting thick out here!
对 我知道 他们就朝着交通拥挤的地方开
Yeah, I know. They're driving right into the heaviest traffic.
这他妈是什么逃跑路线？
What kind of escape route is that?
他们可能不是想逃跑 他们可能是有个目标
Maybe they're not trying to escape. Maybe they're heading somewhere.
- 潜在的目标？- 是的
- Possible target? - Yes.
有很多金属的地方
Some place with a lot of metal.
- 他们要把它毁掉 大家注意！- 兄弟们 你们要阻止他们！
- They're going to blow it up. All units! - Guys, you have to stop them!
是啊我们在努力
Yeah, we're working on it.
我是说立刻！
I mean right now!
他们要在埃菲尔铁塔上引爆一枚弹头！
They're going to detonate one of the warheads on the Eiffel Tower!
碾碎他！
Crush him!
面具人！
Snake!
他在下面 杀了他！
He's underneath. Kill him!
那个红毛的确开始令我愤怒了
That redhead is really starting to piss me off.
该死！
Shit!
哦 老天！
Oh, God!
我接到你了 接到你了
I got you. I got you.
- 干的不错 小家伙 - 喂
- Nice save, slick. - Come on,
别从现在就开始对我动心 该走了
don't start being all nice to me now. Gotta go.
上来！
Get in!
好吧 开伞索 让我们把它拿下！抓紧了 面具人！
All right, Rip, let's take this thing down! Hang on, Snake!
试下这个是否合身 孩子们
Try this on for size, boys.
哦 该死！
Oh, shit!
我们跟丢了！
We lost them!
穿过街对面那座建筑
Cut through that building across the street.
- 门在哪了？- 做一个！
- Where's the door? - Make one!
没错！来吧 开伞索！
Right! Come on, Rip!
我来了 我来了！
I'm coming. I'm coming!
我没看见他们！在哪呢？
I don't have them! Where are they?
- 他们要接近铁塔了 - 我们只有两公里远了
- They're evacuating the Tower. - We're only 2 kilometers away.
面具人 我们没有时间了 你要做些什么
Snake, we're running out of time. You gotta do something.
现在不做就永远没机会
It's now or never.
- 他放弃了 - 他从不会放弃
- He gave up. - He never gives up.
穿过去！
Coming through!
哇 太疯狂了 我从没想过这种
Okay, that was crazy. I didn't expect that.
- 你怎么了？- 我穿过了火车
- What happened to you? - I went through the train.
- 你呢？- 我跳过了它
- What happened to you? - I jumped over it.
- 能这么做？- 是啊我告诉过你读读手册
- You can do that? - Yeah. I told you to read that manual.
有手册？
There's a manual?
下一次 我来开
Next time, I'll drive.
这儿 拿着制动开关
Here. Take the kill switch.
快点 把路让开！
Come on. Get out of the way!
喂 伙计们 他们还活着 而且正在移动
Hey, guys, they're alive and they're on the move.
他们已经激活了弹头 我现在追踪一下制动开关
And they've activated the warhead. I'm tracking the kill switch now.
公爵！公爵 它在男爵夫人身上！
Duke! Duke, it's on the Baroness!
白幽灵拿着一个弹头 而且已上膛了
Storm Shadow has one of the warheads, and it's armed!
都给我闪开！闪开！
Get out of my way! Get out!
出去！
Get out!
鞋很不错
Nice shoes.
你去追弹头 我去追制动开关
You get the warhead, I'll get the kill switch.
好 这就去
Yeah, I'm on it.
该死 那个忍者真快！
Damn, that ninja's fast!
不
No.
哦 不！
Oh, no!
- 超级惨烈了 - 不
- Bloody hell. - No.
他们会吃掉整个城市的
They're gonna eat through the entire city.
公爵 你一定要按下开关！
Duke, you have to hit that kill switch!
哦 老天
Oh, God.
伤害解除
Disarmed.
恭喜了 公爵 你刚刚拯救了巴黎
Congratulations, Duke. You just saved Paris.
或者说大部分巴黎
Or at least most of it.
- 那是血吗？- 意大利面条酱 别问了
- Is that blood? - Spaghetti sauce. Don't ask.
- 他们抓走了公爵 - 我们知道
- They got Duke. - We know.
- 你在做什么？- 插入他的大脑皮层里
- What are you doing? - Plugging into his cerebral cortex.
我讨厌打断你
I hate to break the news to you,
不过我觉得在他死掉的情况下 他不会给你什么信息
but I don't think he's gonna give you much in his dead condition.
大脑在人死的几分钟内还会存活
The brain survives a couple of minutes after death.
我们可以提取他最近的记忆搭载的电脉冲
We can retrieve the electrical impulses from his most recent memories
- 然后把它们转化成图像 - 那么我们能找到公爵么？
- and convert them to images. - Well, can we find Duke?
我们首先要找到其他三个弹头
We need to find the other three warheads first.
如果这个家伙记得回家的路 或许我们都能找到
If this guy remembers his way home, maybe we can find both.
好了 图像出来了 让我们看看这个家伙从哪来
Okay, here come the images. Let's see where this guy's been.
- 他还活着 - 不可能
- He's still alive! - He can't be.
有3寸的针头扎在他脑袋里！
He's got 3-inch needles in his head!
- 喂 死人不会跳霹雳舞！- 怎么回事 断路器？
- Hey, dead guys don't breakdance! - What's happening, Breaker?
- 纳米虫 正在吃掉他 - 一定是某种自我毁灭装置
- Nanomites, they're eating him. - Must be some sort of self-destruct.
- 快点 断路器！- 快 快 快
- Hurry, Breaker! - Come on, come on, come on.
不 不！
No. No!
不 不 不！
No, no, no!
美丽的纳米技术
The beauty of nanotechnology.
- 我们被耍了 - 放心 我得到了可以得到的一切
- We are screwed. - Relax. I got everything I could.
什么？那你刚才说「不 不 不」是什么意思？
What? Then what the hell was the, "No, no, no, no!" for?
那是给麦卡伦看的
That was for McCullen.
- 他们在看着我们 - 好吧 那你都得到了什么？
- They were watching us. - Okay. So what did you get?
实际上 不很多 只是些图像
Actually, not that much. Just images.
不是吧 老兄 你说过你是这方面最好的
Come on, Frenchie. I thought you said you was the best at this.
- 我是这方面最好的！- 好吧
- I am the best at this! - All right.
- 没人能做到我做的 - 好
- Nobody can do what I just did. - Okay.
等等 不
Wait, no.
不是我们做的 我们是好人
We didn't do it. We're the good guys.
- 把你的手举起来 开伞索 - 我们没时间了！
- Put your hands up, Rip. - We don't have time for this!
我们不被允许跟友军开战
We're not allowed to engage with friendly forces.
他们对我看起来不够友好 我要去救我的兄弟
They don't look too friendly to me. I gotta get my boy.
- 看 队长… - 开伞索！
- Look, Captain… - Rip!
我们还在追寻剩下3个弹头的下落 先生
We're still trying to locate the three remaining warheads, sir.
- 特种兵们怎么样了？- 他们被羁押了
- What's the status of the Joes? - They've been detained.
- 法国人相当沮丧 - 他们当然沮丧
- The French are pretty upset. - Of course they're upset.
让我见法国大使
Get me the French Ambassador.
（法国反恐局）
几秒钟内被一个导弹击中…
In a matter of seconds by a strike by a missile…
喂 不 不要！
Hey, no, no!
请不要碰它！那是我的设备 非常的…
Please don't touch that! That's my equipment. It's very…
好吧 他已经碰了
Okay, he's touching it.
- 干的不错啊强人 - 不是他的错
- Nice going, slick. - It's not his fault.
他只是太感性了
He's just emotional.
- 让我来看看 - 我没事
- Here, let me look at that. - I'm fine.
只想帮帮你 将军！
Just trying to help. General!
法国人同意让你们离开 条件是你们不能再回来
The French have agreed to let you all go on the condition that none of you return.
永远
Ever.
- 永远？- 这就算不错的了
- Never? - It could be worse.
你说永远是什么意思？是说再也不能 永远不能？
What do you mean by never? Like, never, never, ever?
还有件事
There's more.
你们所有人都被你们各自国家的头头召回
All of you have been recalled by your respective heads of state.
A小队要返回地下基地
Team Alpha is to return to the Pit.
那公爵怎么办？
What about Duke?
联系麦卡伦 告诉他我们带着3个弹头
Call McCullen. Tell him we have the three warheads.
马上就做
Right away.
为什么你不杀了我？
Why didn't you just kill me?
麦卡伦对你有一些特别的想法
McCullen has something special in mind for you.
麦卡伦
McCullen.
你到底怎么了？
What happened to you?
你现在在乎了？
Now you care?
好吧
Okay.
我很抱歉
I am sorry.
我抱歉雷克斯的事
I'm sorry about Rex.
我抱歉我未能把雷克斯带回家
I'm sorry that I couldn't bring Rex home.
我还抱歉那件事以后我无法再面对你
And I'm so sorry that I couldn't face you afterwards.
是啊每个人都有抱歉的事情
Well, everybody's sorry about something.
[日语] 恭喜成为顶级高手！
师傅！
Master!
师傅
Master.
那么 公爵怎么办？我们就这样把他忘了？
Okay, so what about Duke? We're just gonna forget about him?
我们有我们的命令
We've got our orders.
老兄你看 如果是你们中的一人会怎么办？
Look, man, what if it was one of your guys?
如果是红发女或者断路器呢？你们又会怎么做？
What if it was Scarlett or Breaker? What would you do then?
看起来非常远 或许是个好地方作为基地
Looks pretty remote. Might be a good location for a base.
雪！让我想到了什么 地球的三分之一？
Snow. That leaves us with what, a third of the earth?
呃…
Yeah.
- 喂 那是麦卡伦的影子么？- 发现了什么？
- Hey, is that McCullen's shadow? - What you got?
- 球面三角学 - 我一定没选那门课
- Spherical trigonometry. - I must have missed that class.
如果你知道物体的高度 和影子的长度
If you know the height of the object, the length of the shadow,
还有捕捉到的图像的时间日期
and the time and date that the image was captured,
- 你就可以找出他的位置 - 这就是我为什么没选这门课
- you can figure out its location. - That's why I missed that class.
好的 断路器 给我看看 我们发现了什么？
All right, Breaker, give it to me. What have we got?
你看 麦卡伦是180身高 他的影子是46厘米
Okay. McCullen is 180 centimeters tall. His shadow is 46 centimeters.
这个图像有6%的衰期
This image has decayed 6%,
也就是说在51小时17分钟前
which means it's 51 hours and 17 minutes old.
那就是在北极冰冠
That's at the polar icecap.
- 重载 - 是的
- Heavy. - Yep.
你怎么看 先生？
What do you say, sir?
我说你们被命令回到地下基地
I said you've been ordered back to the Pit,
但是我没说何时 而且我也没说走哪条路
but I didn't say when and I didn't say which route to take.
或许走向北的路
Maybe a northern one.
很多的冰川
That is a lot of ice.
上千英里的跨度 10层楼的厚度
Thousands of miles across and 10 stories thick.
找到麦卡伦的基地好似在煤矿里找根针
Locating McCullen's base will be like finding a needle in a coal mine.
- 干草垛 - 哦 对
- Haystack. - Oh, right.
在煤矿里找干草垛
Haystack in a coal mine.
不！麦卡伦留着他有用！
No! McCullen has plans for him!
够了！
Enough!
你是怎么打算的？
And what was your plan?
在冰面上跑3000英里？
Run 3, 000 miles across the ice?
愚蠢的战士
Stupid soldier.
带走
Move it.
- 很奇怪 - 什么？
- That's strange. - What?
当他们偷走箱子的时候 我设置了我的接收仪
When they stole the weapons case, I set my scanner
一旦追踪信号返回 就可以收到
to look out for the tracking beacon in case it came back on.
- 而刚刚我收到了 - 那是我兄弟！
- And it just came back on. - That's my boy!
还剩三个
Three left.
把这些弹头装在导弹上 我要一小时内准备好发射
Take the warheads to the missiles. I want them ready to launch in one hour.
很快就好
It will be done.
我的湖中女神
My beautiful Lady of the Lake.
让你很不自在？
This bother you?
很搞笑的 不是么？整个世界的权力均衡即将改变
It's funny, isn't it? The entire balance of power in the world about to shift,
而两个家伙还在这争女孩
two guys can still have a stare-down over who gets the girl.
我会让你非常不高兴的
I'm gonna make you very unhappy.
- 我已经很不高兴了 - 起来！
- I'm already unhappy. - Get up!
生物相机的影像正在传回来
Video from the Aqua Cam is coming online now.
我的老天
Bloody hell.
他们在北极冰冠下建了一个军事基地
They've built a military base under the polar icecap.
完美的地点 几乎不可探测到 很容易防御
It's the perfect location. Nearly undetectable, easily defensible.
- 公爵一定在里面 - 还有弹头
- Duke's got to be in there somewhere. - And the warheads.
我们要找到一条秘密的路进去
We have to find a quiet way to get inside.
电梯缆绳 在地表有入口
Elevator cables. They've got a surface entrance.
大家看 还有些其他的 转入声纳模式
Guys, there's something else. Going to sonar view.
他们在冰层里打穿了隧道
They've got tunnels running through the ice pack.
喂 看 他们有自己的攻击潜艇
Hey, look, they've got their own attack subs.
好 那是什么？
Okay, what's that?
- 导弹筒 - 一定用于发射纳米弹头
- Missile tubes. - Must be for the nanomite warheads.
我们上升 我要从外面给他们点麻烦 让他们忙不过来
Take us up. I'll create a distraction from outside and keep them busy
当你们从上面潜入到建筑内 我们会找到公爵
while you lot infiltrate the facility from above. We'll find Duke…
- 拿回弹头 - 杀死所有的坏蛋
- Grab the warheads. - Kill all the bad guys.
你们知道 A组在直接的命令下
As you all know, Team Alpha is under direct orders
即将返回他们各自国家的基地
to return to their respective national bases.
但是我有些事情需要做 这样做会违反命令
But I have something I need to do which goes against all orders.
所以如果你们有谁决定现在离开
So, if any of you decide that you have to leave now,
我一定不会拦着你
I will certainly not hold it against you.
好的
Okay, then.
你们打算怎么用那些弹头？
What are you gonna do with the warheads?
你真是训练有素 很好
You take to your training well. That's good.
仍然想发掘出一些情报
Still trying to develop intel.
- 那么你不会介意告诉我 - 不是很显然么？
- So you won't mind telling me. - Isn't it obvious?
我是生意人 我要用了它们
I'm a businessman. I'm going to use them.
如果你发射了那些弹头 上百万人会死
Millions of people are gonna die if you launch those warheads,
那么你会得到什么呢？
so what is it that you want?
在这个星球上的每一个男人女人小孩身上 注入恐惧
To strike fear into the hearts of every man, woman and child on the planet.
然后他们就会转而投向最有力量的人
Then they'll turn to the person with the most power.
你？
You?
不 不是我
No, not me.
- 你还没有看到全部 - 那么告诉我
- You're not seeing the whole picture. - Then tell me.
我不想浪费了惊喜
I don't wanna spoil the surprise.
客人到
Guests.
见一下纳米科技背后的天才吧
Meet the genius behind all my nanotechnology.
天才？你太客气了
Genius? You are too kind.
你可以看到 我们正装载纳米弹头
As you can see, we are loading my nanomite warheads
利用高速导弹
into the high-V missiles.
当达到最大速度时 会有5马赫
Once at maximum velocity, Mach 5,
甚至连特种部队都没有技术来抓住它们
not even the Joes have the technology to catch them.
那么他是谁？又一个新兵？
So, who's this? Another recruit?
不过是一个不太情愿的
Albeit a rather unwilling one.
我会为他准备好的
I'll prepare him for the procedure.
所有队伍注意 我是霍克将军
All teams, listen up, this is General Hawk.
行动开始 重复一遍 行动开始
The mission is a go. I say again, the mission is a go.
好运 特种兵们
Good luck, Joes.
- 所有队伍都部署完毕 长官 - 给我一个卫星信号
- The teams have been deployed, sir. - Get me a satellite uplink.
我要看见那里发生的一切
I wanna see everything that's going on down there.
你发现了什么了？
You picking up anything?
没有 仪器上什么都没显示
Negative. There's nothing on the scanner.
- 打得不错 - 谢谢
- Nice shooting. - Thank you.
我们离迈阿密真的很远啊
We're a long way from Miami.
那是夜鸦 他们的确造了一架
That's a Night Raven. They actually built one.
看起来很快 那个麦卡伦搞了不少经费
Looks fast. That McCullen got some gadgets.
MARS工业生产了这个星球上70%的武器
MARS Industries manufactures 70% of all arms on this planet.
70%
70%.
你知道这点吗 公爵？
Did you know that, Duke?
麦卡伦的计划里包括两个方面 剑与盾
There are two sides to McCullen's operation, the Sword and the Shield.
剑就是创造和贩卖武器
The Sword creates and sells weaponry.
盾就是创造出防御性科技 例如高科技掩体
The Shield creates defensive technology, like high-tech bunkers,
可以保护你免受任何袭击
which are supposed to protect one from anything
无论是核爆炸还是纳米弹头
from a nuclear blast to a nanomite warhead.
不幸的是 我当时避难的掩体
Unfortunately, the bunker in which I took shelter
还只是个雏形
was just a prototype.
你是谁？
Who are you?
雷克斯？
Rex?
你这个婊子养的！安娜安葬了你！
You son of a bitch! Ana buried you!
感人的仪式 我肯定
Moving ceremony, I'm sure.
鸣枪仪式
The three-volley salute.
战场荣耀 折叠的国旗在她胳膊上
Boots on the ground. A folded flag in her arms.
为什么？为什么你不出现呢？
Why? Why didn't you just come in?
因为我发现了一些东西
Because I discovered something.
…项目编号23
…subject number 23.
这只会有点疼
This will only hurt a little.
即将发生的 会更美
What comes next, more so.
听着 光头博士不惜任何代价
Listen, Mindbender, do whatever it takes.
我也会
So will I.
记得 科学需要献身
Remember, science requires sacrifice.
- 很美吧 不是么？- 待着别动！
- It's beautiful, isn't it? - Stay where you are!
你要开枪射我吗？
Are you going to shoot me?
这些不是化学或者核物质 对吧？
These aren't chemical or nuclear, are they?
不
No.
他们是更好的东西
They're something much, much better.
很美丽
It is beautiful.
纳米螨虫 它超越了…
Nanomites, it's beyond…
它比这领域其他任何人做的都要超前
It's light years ahead of what anyone else is doing in the field.
空袭警报
Proximity alert.
空中袭击临近 所有人员到掩体内
Aerial attack imminent. All personnel to the bunker.
快 快！干什么？
Come on. Come on! What?
你在干什么？不要关门 不要…
What are you doing? Don't close that. Don't…
如果我们活着 我会让你见识一切
If we live, I'll show you everything.
我们在爆炸中幸存了 不过…
We survived that blast, somewhat.
光头博士和我带着他的研究逃掉了 而我完善了它
And Dr. Mindbender and I escaped with his research, which I perfected
而现在将带给你第一手的体验
and which you will now experience first-hand.
安娜知道这件事吗 关于你？
Does Ana know about this? About you?
不 她不会知道的
No, and she never will.
开始发射进程
Commence the launch sequence.
开始发射进程 时间倒数 四三二一
Commencing launch sequence. T-minus four, three, two, one.
点燃主引擎
Ignite primary engines.
引擎启动
We have ignition.
他们正在发射导弹！
They're launching the missiles!
我们失去了北京的导弹 失去了3号弹头 先生
We lost the Beijing missile. Warhead three is down, sir.
- 所有防御戒备 - 好的 先生
- Alert all defenses. - Yes, sir.
他来了
He's here.
- 另外两个怎么办？- 我们要找到启动开关
- What about the other two? - We gotta find the kill switches.
他们太远了超出了范围
They're already way too far out of range.
要有人飞上去然后把它们打下来
Somebody has to get up there and shoot those things down.
哦 我猜那该是我了
Well, I guess that's me.
- 先生 - 什么情况？
- Sir. - What is it?
战略中心追踪到了3个弹头
STRATCOM is tracking three warheads
刚刚从北极冰冠发射了
that have just launched off the polar icecap.
其中一个立刻被打掉
One was downed immediately.
另外两个现在进入了上层大气
The other two are currently entering the upper atmosphere.
我们要把你送入掩体里 先生
We need to get you down to the bunker, sir.
可他们还没提任何条件 他们怎么想的？
Well, they haven't made any demands. What's their plan?
这个东西真的酷
Now, this is very cool.
- 是的 不过你能飞起来吗？- 我可以飞起来任何东西
- Yeah, but can you fly it? - I can fly anything.
你只要找到方法指引我找到弹头
You just find a way to guide me to those warheads.
- 嗯 开伞索… - 什么？
- Right. Ripcord… - Yeah?
- 祝好运 - 谢谢
- Good luck. - Thanks.
- 喂 帮我个忙 - 什么？
- Hey, do me a favor. - Yeah?
- 救下公爵 - 没问题
- Save Duke. - You got it.
我们走！
Let's go!
地上是压力板还有镭射保护
The floor is pressure-plated and laser-protected.
任何大于1夸特重量的东西接触地面 都会被烤熟
Anything larger than a quarter that touches that floor gets fried.
你丢下我不管 公爵 看看我
You left me for dead, Duke, and look at me.
现在你会知道怪物会是什么样子
Now you'll know what it's like to be a monster.
- 我们时间不多了 - 安娜？
- We don't have much time. - Ana?
哦 我的天
Oh, my God.
- 安娜！- 警卫 来控制室！
- Ana! - Security, to the operating chamber!
- 雷克斯！- 我按下这个 她就死
- Rex! - I press this, she dies.
- 你对你自己的姐姐这么做！- 我爱我的姐姐
- You did this to your own sister! - I loved my sister.
你知道我的死让她成什么样了 而你又离开？
Do you have any idea the state she was in with me dead, you gone?
你曾经感觉到真正的孤独吗？
Have you ever felt truly alone?
我给了她一种疗伤的办法 我给了她意志
I gave her a way to deal with the pain. I gave her purpose.
你可以告诉她你活着 这一切就不必发生！
You could have stopped all of this just by letting her know you were alive!
科学需要献身
Science requires sacrifice.
她那样子都是因为你！
All she's done was because of you!
还有你 公爵 你离弃了她
And because of you, Duke. You abandoned her.
- 我们不要忘记这一点 - 我要杀了你 雷克斯
- Let's not forget that point. - I'm gonna kill you, Rex.
- 她还活着吗？- 现在活着
- Is she still alive? - For now.
我以为我们完全控制住了 你说过这不会发生的
I thought we had complete control. You said this couldn't happen.
我也以为不会
I didn't think it could.
我还没见过有人凌驾在程序之上 哪怕是片刻
I've never seen anyone override the programming, even momentarily.
她因为他做到了
She did this for him.
痛苦一定在折磨她
The pain must have been excruciating.
你要做的就是
What you'll have to do
小心地把镭射板的核心重新接线…
is to rewire the laser panel's brain by carefully…
- 或者你可以直接捅破它 - 我是红发女 我们进来了
- Or you can just stab it. - This is Scarlett. We're in.
派遣特种潜艇！
Deploy the SHARCs!
潜艇1-3号分离
Detaching SHARCs 1-3…
分离潜艇 ABCD
Detaching SHARCs Alpha, Bravo, Charlie, Delta.
- 全速前进 - 分离潜艇
- Full speed ahead. - Detaching SHARCs.
潜艇VFT进入侧翼位置
SHARCs Victor, Franklin, Tango into flanking positions.
好了 大家 组成攻击阵型
All right, boys. Attack formation.
扇形展开 等待特种兵们打乱阵型
Fan out. Wait until the Joes break formation.
保持紧密 他们来了
Stay tight. Here they come.
- 激发脉冲大炮！- 正在做 先生
- Fire up the pulse cannon! - We're on it, sir.
- 我会下手的！- 放下！
- I'll do it! - Put it down!
在于你 公爵
Your choice, Duke.
给脉冲大炮充电
Charging pulse cannon.
大家保持在敌人潜艇周围
Everybody stay tight on the enemy craft.
不要暴露在大炮面前
Don't let that cannon catch you out in the open.
10点钟方向来了
Bogey at 10 o'clock.
我中弹了！我中了！我中了！
I'm hit! I'm hit! I'm hit!
2枚导弹 所有遥测和推进系统工作正常
Missile 2, all telemetry and propulsion systems nominal.
- 开伞索 能听见我吗？- 清清楚楚 老兄
- Ripcord, can you hear me? - Loud and clear, buddy.
开到6马赫 太爽了！
Doing Mach 6 and loving it!
来吧 该告诉我你们的知道的了
Come on, girl. Time to show me what you got.
好的 开伞索 我有其他两枚弹头的坐标
Okay, Rip, I have the coordinates of the other two warheads.
最近的目标是莫斯科 你要首先打掉这个
The closest target is Moscow. You'll have to hit that one first.
目标二是华盛顿
Target two is Washington.
你在这个掩体里会安全的 先生
You'll be safe down in this bunker, sir.
- 还有多久会袭击到这？- 十七分钟 先生
- How soon before it strikes the city? - Seventeen minutes, sir.
- 现在就看特种部队的了 - 请快进入 总统先生
- It's all up to the Joes now. - Please hurry, Mr. President.
我们要把门锁住
We need to get you buttoned up.
霍克将军 引擎被击中 我们完全残废了
General Hawk, we've lost our engines. We're completely disabled.
有人去做掉那个大炮吗 那个艇里有200名特种兵
Somebody take out that damn cannon. There's 200 Joes on that sub.
我们在做 先生 好吧 面具人
We're on it, sir. All right, Snake,
大炮控制室应该就在那
the cannon control room should be right there,
所有镭射管道汇集处
where all the laser conduits converge.
你认为她爱过你？你想过跟她度过一生？
Did you think she loved you? Did you imagine your life with her?
我知道的是 你们都不配拥有她
All I know is, neither one of you deserve her.
- 就这样吧 她死定了！- 不要这样 雷克斯！
- That's it. She dies! - Don't do it, Rex!
快
Come on.
我要带你出去
I'm gonna get you out of here.
起来！
Get up!
你跟我走！
You're coming with me.
开伞索 莫斯科导弹4分钟内即将到达
Ripcord, the Moscow missile will impact in four minutes.
好的 我看见它了
All right, I got a visual on it.
正前方
Dead ahead.
你要在它重入大气层前把它干下来
You have to knock it down before it re-enters the atmosphere.
如果那些纳米虫击中了地面 一切都毁了
If those nanomites hit the ground, it's all over.
他们会吃掉整个城市
They'll destroy the whole city.
休斯顿 出现了问题
Houston, we have a problem.
- 火控系统不在这 - 什么意思 不在那？
- The fire controls are not in here. - What do you mean, not in there?
我是说 我到处都找不到
I mean, I don't see them anywhere.
那就一定是声控的
It must be voice-activated.
好吧 开火！
Okay. Fire!
发射！轰炸！开枪呀！
Shoot! Blast away! Bust a cap!
- 没反应！- 我猜是用另一种语言
- Nothing's happening! - I bet it's in a different language.
等一下 麦卡伦是苏格兰人 或许飞机听凯尔特语指令
Wait a minute. McCullen is Scottish. Maybe the plane responds to Celtic.
- 试试「铁尼」 - 什么？
- Try Teine. - What?
- 铁尼 是苏格兰凯尔特语开火的意思 - 好的 收到
- Teine. It's Celt, Scottish for fire. - Okay, got it.
你是最棒的 你刚拯救了莫斯科
Nice going, ace. You just saved Moscow.
本职工作而已 指引我去华盛顿吧
Just doing my job. Now guide me to Washington.
好 好 谢谢 真是好消息 我会告诉他
Yeah. Yeah, thanks, that's great news. I'll let him know.
先生 一名特种兵射掉了发向莫斯科的弹头
Sir, one of the Joes shot down the warhead heading for Moscow.
感谢上帝
Thank God.
你在做什么？哦 上帝！
What are you doing? Oh, my God!
搞定了
It's done.
你好 总统先生 麦卡伦先生向您表示问候
Hello, Mr. President. Mr. McCullen sends his regards.
哦 上帝啊
Oh, my God.
那么 这就是你们的目的
So, that's what this is all about.
好吧 大家保持紧密
All right. Keep tight, boys.
所有武器对准那门大炮 电动鱼雷发射！
All guns on that cannon. Torpedoes away!
我刚失去了侧翼
I've just lost my wingman.
重新瞄准特种兵潜艇
Retargeting Joe submarine.
我发射了
I've got a shot.
脉冲大炮故障 脉冲大炮故障
Pulse cannon fault. Pulse cannon fault.
大炮控制失效
Cannon now offline.
- 整个该死的系统都瘫了 - 我正试着重新连接控制
- The whole damn system's down. - I'm trying to bring it back online.
这次你死了
Now you die.
立刻启动
Launch immediately.
- 找条路从冰层往上走 - 好的 先生
- Chart a course up to the ice pack. - Yes, sir.
- 我们要跟着雷克斯和麦卡伦 - 怎么会是雷克斯？
- We gotta go after Rex and McCullen. - How could it be Rex?
嗨 红发女 我是公爵！
Hey, Scarlett, it's Duke!
- 他看起来还好 - 不过他怎么跟她在一起？
- He looks fine. - But what's he doing with her?
我们跟踪了麦卡伦的潜艇 他在冰层里行进
Okay, we got a track on McCullen's sub. He's headed up into the ice pack.
公爵 我们后面！
Duke, behind us!
貌似他们冲我们来的 安娜 打掉那些家伙
Looks like they're onto us. Ana, shoot those guys.
乐意效劳
Love to.
当我们师父被杀 你发誓要一直沉默
When our master was killed, you took a vow of silence.
现在你也将不留一言地死去
Now you will die without a word.
好了 我看见第二个了
All right, the second one in my sights.
好的 开伞索 你在它进入低层大气前只有30秒的时间
Okay, Rip, you only got 30 seconds before it enters the lower atmosphere.
知道了！
I got you!
- 开伞索 你失手了 - 弹头已经进入了…
- Ripcord, you missed. - The warhead has entered
低层大气层
the lower atmosphere.
我知道 我知道！我在努力 我在努力！
I know, I know! I'm on it, I'm on it!
该死！
Shit!
- 我没法摆脱这些家伙 - 公爵 我打光了！
- I can't shake these guys. - Duke, I'm out!
- 好吧 看看我们这还有什么 - 黑光 分离器 镭射炮
- All right, let's see what we got here. - Black Ray, Eliminator, LAW.
镭射炮 听起来不错
Laser Artillery Weapon. That sounds good.
- 红发女！- 嗨 公爵
- Scarlett! - Hey, Duke!
我去跟着麦卡伦和雷克斯
I'm going after McCullen and Rex.
你们大家最好赶紧离开这
You guys better get the hell out of there.
不行 开伞索还有一个弹头没打下来
I can't. Rip has one more warhead to take down.
开伞索 他在哪？
Rip, where is he?
导弹刚刚分离了 就要引爆了
The missile's just gone drone. It's going in for the kill!
先生 有一艘敌人的螳螂潜艇跟在后面
Sir, there's a hostile Mantis craft coming up behind us.
- 关上门 - 好的
- Seal the door. - Sir.
给你这个
There you are.
一枚穿过去了 我打中了他们
One got through. I hit them!
公爵！他们在后面！
Duke! They're back!
马上就热闹了 321
Going hot in three, two, one.
一定还有其它路绕到雷克斯和麦卡伦前面
There's gotta be another way around to Rex and McCullen.
寻找新的选择路线
Charting new course for alternate route.
距离爆炸还有20秒
Twenty seconds until impact.
快 快 快
Come on, come on, come on.
你离得太紧了 开伞索！退一些！
You're too close, Rip! Back off!
事实上 我想我刚刚正好
Actually, I think I'm just about close enough.
他带着纳米虫回到上层大气
He's taking the nanomites back into the upper atmosphere.
开伞索 离开飞机！
Ripcord, get out of that plane!
就要到了！
Almost there!
弹射 开伞索 弹射！
Eject, Ripcord, eject!
他做到了 他真的做到了
He did it. He actually did it.
开伞索？
Ripcord?
开伞索！
Ripcord!
我没跟你说过不要对我吼吗？
Didn't I ask you not to yell at me?
大家注意！还有许多特种兵在那里有危险
Everybody, listen up! We still have a lot of Joes out there in harm's way.
让我们带他们回家
Let's bring them home.
- 成功了吗？- 是的 成功了
- Did it work? - Yes, yes, it worked.
好的 因为我想我又将被逮捕了
Good. Because I think I'm about to get arrested, again.
不要动！
Don't move!
- 喂 喂 自己人 自己人！- 举起手！
- Hey, hey, same team, same team! - Hands up!
自己人
Same team.
好吧 好 好
Okay, okay, okay.
- 我们什么情况？- 失去了船尾推进器和声纳
- What's our status? - We've lost aft thrusters and the sonar.
- 我们瞎了 - 杀了他们 杀了所有特种兵
- We're running blind. - Kill them. Kill all the Joes.
- 炸掉冰层 - 这就做 先生
- Detonate the ice pack. - Right away, sir.
他们正通知告诉其它艇终止行动 他要炸掉冰层
They're telling the other ships to abort. He's gonna blow the ice pack.
我是公爵 呼叫所有特种兵 冰层开始坠下！
This is Duke calling all Joes. The ice pack's coming down!
上吨的钢铁和冰
There's a ton of steel and ice
- 冲着你们去了！- 什么？
- headed your way! - What?
大家后退 立刻后退！
Everybody, pull back! Pull back now!
门！开门 开门！把门打开！
Door! The door, the door! Get the door!
快！
Come on!
安娜 我们该立刻离开这 方便快捷 安全可靠的路
Ana, we could get out of here right now, free and clear, safe and sound.
- 我们来搞定他们吧 - 这才是我的安娜
- Let's get them. - That's my girl.
- 这里要爆炸了 公爵 - 我不会让那两个家伙跑掉
- This is cutting it close, Duke. - I'm not letting those two get away.
快点 大家快离开那！
Come on, guys, get out of there!
面具人！
Snake!
- 我是红发女 我们安全了 - 我是公爵 我们也安全
- This is Scarlett. We're all clear. - This is Duke. We're clear, too.
嘿 瞧瞧我们！
Yo, Joe!
好喔！
Yeah!
现在我们有了属于我们的时刻
Now that we have a moment to ourselves,
我计划了一些事情
I've designed something
- 特别为你准备的 詹姆斯 - 不！
- especially for you, James. - No!
这只会有一点疼
This will only hurt a little.
即将发生的 会更美
What comes next, more so.
纳米虫 完美的小治疗法师
Nanomites, perfect little healers.
我好不容易继承了麦卡伦家族的祖脉
I've finally taken my place in a long line of McCullens.
詹姆斯·麦卡伦不复存在 现在你是迪斯特罗
James McCullen is no more. Now you are Destro.
你对我做了什么？
What have you done to me?
到了眼镜蛇崛起和显露的时刻了
The time has come for the cobra to rise up and reveal himself.
你要叫我司令
You will call me Commander.
我是豪瑟上尉 准备接受我方登艇
This is Captain Duke Hauser. Prepare to be boarded.
先生
Sir.
你很坚韧 公爵 我愿意给你那么高的评价
You are relentless, Duke. I'll give you that much.
怎么才能不让我把你炸开到水面上呢？
And what's to stop me from blowing you out of the water?
自我保护 我会帮你的 雷克斯
Self-preservation. I'm taking you in, Rex.
你跟谁的队伍？
You and what army?
我的队伍
My army.
你听着 公爵 这只是个开始
You know, Duke, this has only just begun.
我会等着你的
I'll be waiting for you.
我从未见过这种编码 我是说 身体上看她还好
I've never seen encoding like this. I mean, physically, she's fine,
不过当雷克斯给他们输入了程序 他就没想要取出来
but when Rex programmed them, he sure didn't want them taken out.
- 那你们就没什么可做的了？- 会需要一些时间
- So there's nothing you can do for her? - It'll take some time,
但是我们会取出来的
but we'll take them out.
直到我们把那些东西从你的脑袋里取出来
Till we get those things out of your head,
貌似你要每天都待在这了
looks like you're gonna be seeing a lot of me around here.
你没法救我的 公爵 没人可以 我做了太多的坏事
You can't save me, Duke. No one can, not after all I've done.
你看 那不是你
Look, that wasn't you.
我不会放弃你的
I'm not giving up on you.
- 哥们 我们看起来很帅 - 嗯 你最好习惯这种
- Man, we look good. - Yeah, well, you better get used to it.
重载认为你们俩该待着永远别走
Heavy Duty thinks you guys ought to stick around permanently.
那么是你在问我们喽？
So, you're asking us, right?
一定是 因为他的语气不像是发问
Yeah, 'cause he didn't sound like he was asking.
因为你一定会被邀请加入特种部队
'Cause you gotta be asked to join the G.I. Joes.
是我邀请
I'm asking.
好的 我加入
Well, I'm in.
- 你对这件事怎么看？- 我觉得我非常的感性
- How do you feel about this? - I feel very emotional.
所有特种兵集结 准备执行猫鼬行动
All Joes mobilize and ready check for Operation Mongoose.
所有地面运输部队在格林兄弟基地集结
All ground transports, rendezvous at Base Brothers Grimm.
所有咆哮猎人号在罗马废墟基地集结
All Howler Hunters will rendezvous at Base Roman Ruin.
好运 特种兵
Good luck, Joes.
总统先生 真高兴见到您
Mr. President, it's good to see you.
- 谢谢你 还有你 - 您安全地回来真好 先生
- Thank you. And you. - It's nice to have you back safely, sir.
- 谢谢你 约翰 - 欢迎回来 先生
- Thank you. John. - Welcome back, sir.
谢谢 非常感谢大家
Thank you. Thank you all so much.